As my husband,
作为我的丈夫，
I want to take care of my wife's face.
我想照顾我妻子的脸。
After this, I will definitely serve the double empire.
以后我一定会为双帝国服务。
May you be united.
愿你们团结一致。
All of you!
你们所有人！
Take off your clothes!
脱掉你的衣服！
Stop!
停止！
Tuan Mucun,
Tuan Mucun,
today is the wedding day
今天是结婚纪念日
my nephew.
我的侄子。
Your actions
你的行动
do this
做这个
Something happened, sir.
有事发生了，先生。
However, our cooperation
然而我们的合作
we must continue.
我们必须继续。
Since we want to work together,
既然我们想一起工作，
give the surface only
只给出表面
you arrange a woman
你安排一个女人
to check him in the room,
去房间检查他，
okey?
好吧？
Good.
好的。
Take him away.
把他带走。
Jiaping.
Jiaping.
Jiaping, how about you?
嘉平，你呢？
Keep searching.
不停寻找。
Chen Jiaping.
Chen Jiaping.
If you screw up again,
如果你再搞砸的话
big spoon.
大勺子。
The murder at the foot of the hill.
山脚下的谋杀案。
This matter?
这件事？
I do not understand.
我不明白。
How did the killer sneak in?
凶手是如何潜入的？
Besides that,
除此之外，
why did he go to the store room?
他为什么去储藏室？
All this is Zhao 'an's doing.
这一切都是赵安干的。
Zhao'an?
Zhao'an?
Originally, Zhao 'an wanted Ah Kun to identify the peach on the left,
本来兆安是想让阿坤辨认左边的桃子，
didn't think he had caused Shanxia's death.
不认为山夏的死是他造成的。
There are more left twin peaches.
还有更多剩下的双桃。
You mean this peach?
你说的是这个桃子吗？
We investigate.
我们进行调查。
With Zhao 'an too.
与赵安也。
Investigate thoroughly.
彻底调查。
Does he have a problem?
他有问题吗？
The Left Cavalry is in trouble now.
左翼骑兵现在遇到了麻烦。
I can't say he has problems either.
我也不能说他有问题。
Your brain is stupid.
你的大脑很愚蠢。
Now, Zhao An is in trouble.
现在，赵安遇到了麻烦。
He can take responsibility
他可以承担责任
This is our chance.
这是我们的机会。
Why?
为什么？
Hands are so cold.
手好冷。
Still shivering.
还在发抖。
A scary thing happened.
可怕的事情发生了。
I'm afraid.
我耽心。
Afraid of what?
怕什么？
Nothing to do with us.
与我们无关。
Know I'm a coward.
知道我是个胆小鬼。
Especially when you see a dead person.
尤其是当你看到一个死人的时候。
Definitely can't sleep well lately.
最近肯定睡不好觉。
Lao.
老挝。
You still remember,
你还记得，
when we were new together,
当我们刚在一起的时候
the late night meal you often take me to eat.
你经常带我去吃的夜宵。
Kedai Cui Hua?
Kedai Cui Hua?
Remember.
记住。
You said, the wedding ceremony is today
你说，婚礼就在今天
ended in a hurry.
匆匆结束了。
I'm not full yet
我还没吃饱
and scared to death.
并吓得要死。
I'm begging you.
我求你。
Take me out to eat again,
又带我出去吃饭
okey?
好吧？
Of.
的。
It's been more than two years
已经过去两年多了
it's late at night we haven't eaten together, right?
这么晚了我们还没一起吃饭吧？
Good.
好的。
Thank You.
谢谢。
So sick, right?
病得很厉害，对吧？
Luckily your heart was not injured.
幸好你的心脏没有受伤。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
Sorry.
对不起。
For not protecting you.
因为没有保护你。
The Japanese do not respect us.
日本人不尊重我们。
Why are you still working for them?
你为什么还为他们工作？
I know.
我知道。
After I get the profit,
当我获得利润后，
let's go, okay?
我们走吧，好吗？
Now,
现在，
I have my own plans.
我有自己的计划。
Trust me.
相信我。
I went to work at a trading bank.
我去一家贸易银行工作。
I am your friend.
我是你的朋友。
You have to go to work in a bank.
你必须去银行工作。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
This is dangerous when working for the Japanese.
为日本人工作时这是危险的。
What are you going to do?
你会怎样做？
After all, what can you do with your shop?
毕竟，您可以用您的商店做什么？
I am an accountant.
我是一名会计师。
After all, I can ask Luo Guanqun to agree.
毕竟我可以请罗冠群同意。
But, the most important thing is that I can go to the bank.
但是，最重要的是我可以去银行。
I can go to the bank.
我可以去银行。
To take care of my husband.
为了照顾我的丈夫。
Your voice is more friendly
你的声音更加友善
more useful than painkillers?
比止痛药更有用？
Scream again.
再次尖叫。
Go away.
离开。
I almost died.
我差点死了。
are you kidding
你在开玩笑吧
I mean it.
我是认真的。
Dear.
亲爱的。
It would be nice if there was no war.
如果没有战争就好了。
All this will end.
这一切都将结束。
I still don't agree
我还是不同意
if you want to go to work
如果你想去上班
You are my wife.
你是我的妻子。
You have to listen to me.
你必须听我的。
Just today.
就是今天。
Just today?
就是今天？
You don't follow me?
你不跟着我吗？
My wound hurts again.
我的伤口又痛了。
Team Leader Zhao,
赵组长，
Shuyun.
Shuyun.
It's me.
这就是我。
Only you don't give up on me.
唯独你不放弃我。
No matter what time,
无论什么时间，
I will not give up on you.
我不会放弃你。
Shuyun,
Shuyun,
why?
为什么？
You are no longer useful.
你不再有用了。
Tuan Mucun!
Tuan Mucun!
Forgive me, sir.
请原谅我，先生。
Awak yang mengahwinkan Chen Jiaping dan Zuo Shuangtao?
Awak yang mengahwinkan Chen Jiaping dan Zuo Shuangtao?
Your plan.
你的计划。
Let Ah Kun go to the wedding venue,
让阿坤去婚礼场地，
to the wedding.
去婚礼。
Your bad ideas come one after another.
你的坏主意接二连三地出现。
The hole was getting bigger.
洞越来越大了。
You are the one who caused the army down the hill
你才是导致大军下山的人
take Ah Kun to the wedding!
带阿坤去参加婚礼！
Ya, ya.
是啊，是啊。
Raised by the bottom of the mountain player himself.
由山底玩家自己养大。
It is not our responsibility.
这不是我们的责任。
What? We...
什么？我们...
No, I...
不，我...
I said it wrong.
我说错了。
I...
我...
I have understood.
我明白了。
You mean
你的意思是
death of a relief player
救援队员死亡
I am also responsible for it.
我也有责任。
You want to tell me
你想告诉我
how can a good player die?
一个好球员怎么会死呢？
to yourself?
对你自己？
Don't dare, can't.
不敢，不能。
I... I don't dare and I won't do that.
我……我不敢，我也不会那样做。
I will not and dare not.
我不会也不敢。
Diam!
迪亚姆！
Diam.
直径。
Don't, Chief Mumura. Listen.
别这样，穆村队长。听。
I am raising funds for the launch of Project Shan
我正在为 Shan 项目的启动筹集资金
for the launch of the Shan Plan.
启动掸邦计划。
You killed me Zhao 'an?
你杀了我赵安？
Its okay.
没关系。
My life is worthless.
我的生命毫无价值。
However, funds were not enough.
然而，资金还不够。
It will slow down the Shan Project process.
它将减慢掸邦项目的进程。
It will delay the success of the empire.
这会延缓帝国的成功。
You want to threaten me?
你想威胁我吗？
I'm afraid.
我耽心。
I don't dare and I won't do that.
我不敢也不会这么做。
Diam!
迪亚姆！
Diam.
直径。
Zhao 'an.
Zhao 'an.
Actually, your life is gone.
事实上，你的生命已经消失了。
No more.
不再。
It's just kept here temporarily.
只是暂时放在这里。
Fine.
美好的。
If this mission fails again,
如果这次任务再次失败的话
I will waste your life
我会浪费你的生命
like throwing out trash.
就像扔垃圾一样。
Throw it away!
把它扔掉！
In the shit hole.
在屎洞里。
Toilet?
洗手间？
don't kill me
别杀我
please
请
Tuan Mucun.
Tuan Mucun.
Thank You.
谢谢。
Mr Mumura.
穆村先生。
Left, two pics.
左图两张。
Has Your Honor not checked yet?
陛下还没有检查过吗？
Ah Kun's counter indeed
确实是阿坤的柜台
engraved with left peach.
刻有左桃。
I think that's definitely not a coincidence.
我认为这绝对不是巧合。
Trust me.
相信我。
Or is there another possibility?
或者还有另一种可能吗？
This is a trap designed by Ah Kun and the Left Cavalry.
这是阿坤和左骑兵设计的陷阱。
To bring the dancers into the room.
把舞者带进房间。
Trust me.
相信我。
Don't waste your time.
不要浪费你的时间。
Peach on the left.
左边是桃子。
You should know
你应该知道
you should know clearly
你应该清楚地知道
What is the most important task?
最重要的任务是什么？
Of.
的。
I will try my best
我会尽力
to find the two consultants.
找到两位顾问。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
Since they are both married,
既然两人都结婚了，
us
我们
water to keep fish.
水养鱼。
Look at the situation later.
稍后看情况。
How about your wound?
你的伤口怎么样了？
It's impossible to die.
死是不可能的。
Oh yes.
哦是的。
Is the picture I took
照片是我拍的吗
have you washed it?
你洗了吗？
Captured documents are very valuable.
捕获的文档非常有价值。
But,
但，
dokumen Zhao 'an ini
dokumen Zhao 'an ini
when compared to the Shan Plan,
与掸邦计划相比，
even though I don't care.
尽管我不在乎。
Even so,
即使是这样，
It was also a huge success.
这也是一个巨大的成功。
Before this, we only had
在此之前，我们只有
Sushan's previous program.
苏珊之前的节目。
However, I couldn't get any further information.
然而，我无法获得任何进一步的信息。
I have informed my superiors.
我已经通知我的上级了。
Your next assignment
你的下一个任务
is directly investigating the Shan Program.
正在直接调查掸邦计划。
I understand.
我明白。
Oh yes.
哦是的。
Sebelum ini, Luo Guanqun dan Zhao An
Sebelum ini, Luo Guanqun dan Zhao An
pernah mengesyaki Zuo Shuangtao
pernah mengesyaki Zuo Shuangtao
the killer in the foothill warrior murder.
山麓武士谋杀案中的凶手。
But I didn't take it seriously before now.
但之前我并没有认真对待它。
I think that's just a coincidence.
我认为这只是一个巧合。
However, in the wedding ceremony,
然而在婚礼上，
The Left Cavalry's actions were so strange.
左骑兵的举动实在是太奇怪了。
I was thinking,
我刚在想，
is he also a member of the Anti-Japanese Organization?
难道他也是抗日组织的成员？
You are right.
你是对的。
Now, he wants to
现在，他想要
to work in the store.
在商店工作。
Although I do not agree,
虽然我不同意，
based on his character,
根据他的性格，
I can't stop it.
我无法阻止它。
I think,
我认为，
(Will he be the same as me)
（他会和我一样吗）
(There are also hidden tasks.)
（还有隐藏任务。）
I'll report it
我会举报的
I will report to the superiors as soon as possible
我会尽快向上级汇报
to conduct a more detailed investigation.
进行更详细的调查。
However, you are husband and wife now.
不过，你们现在是夫妻了。
No matter what his true identity is,
不管他的真实身份是什么，
the first thing you need to do is
你需要做的第一件事是
is to protect the security of one's own identity.
是为了保护自己的身份安全。
Watch his next move.
观察他的下一步行动。
Don't compromise his mission.
不要妥协他的使命。
The situation is getting more complicated.
情况变得越来越复杂。
Difficult to understand.
很难理解。
Luo Guanqun, I told you.
Luo Guanqun, I told you.
If the pic is less than half a feather from the left,
如果图片距左侧不到半根羽毛，
I will never let you go!
我永远不会让你走！
Why are you so
为什么你这么
why is it so big?
为什么这么大？
look at you
看着你
You are injured, not healed yet.
你受伤了，还没有痊愈。
Rest first before coming to work.
上班前先休息一下。
Isn't it because of you?
还不是因为你吗？
How can you agree with Zuo Shuangtao?
你怎么能同意左双涛的观点呢？
Coming to work here?
来这里工作吗？
Boss Yu came to see me.
于老板来看我了。
I must take care of his face.
我必须照顾他的脸。
After all,
毕竟，
you two go find me now.
你们两个现在就去找我吧。
That's right!
这是正确的！
You don't see
你没有看到
This is our great opportunity.
这是我们的绝佳机会。
Where is she?
她在哪？
Zhao 'an has lost now.
赵安现在已经输了。
We must take this opportunity to attack them.
我们必须利用这个机会攻击他们。
Boss Yu has already talked to me.
于老板已经跟我谈过了。
He has a number of...
他有数个...
There are essential seed oils in the market.
市场上有精油种子油。
For me to make sales.
为了我做销售。
We keep it for three months.
我们将其保存三个月。
Then, spread the rumor.
然后，就散布谣言。
Rapeseed oil has risen suddenly.
菜籽油突然上涨。
Then it was sold...
然后就被卖掉了...
The money has come in.
钱已经进来了。
If not for the Left Cavalry,
如果不是左翼骑兵，
can Boss Yu have a chat with me?
于老板可以和我聊聊吗？
You can't even allow it
你甚至不能允许
Zuo Shuangtao came to work here?
Zuo Shuangtao came to work here?
He came to give a good image.
他来是为了树立一个良好的形象。
Are you afraid he is in danger?
你害怕他有危险吗？
I'm more scared than you.
我比你更害怕。
I do not care.
我不在乎。
You must guarantee.
你必须保证。
That Left Guard
那个左后卫
will not be exposed to hazardous work.
不会从事危险工作。
I guarantee.
我保证。
I have ten thousand guaranteed.
我保证有一万。
Mari.
马里。
Sit down first.
先坐下吧。
Zhao 'an disokong oleh Mucun.
Zhao 'an disokong oleh Mucun.
Who are you?
你是谁？
Not enough to eat.
不够吃。
Who are you to hurt Zhao 'an?
你是谁，竟敢伤害赵安？
What does Mucun want?
木村想要什么？
Business and money.
生意和金钱。
Business and money are with us.
生意和金钱都在我们身边。
Mucun will join the trend.
木村也将加入这一潮流。
Good.
好的。
Everything you said is true.
你说的一切都是真的。
Hope you
希望你
do not forget me
不要忘了我
do not forget me.
不要忘了我。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
Forget who?
忘记谁了？
I will never forget you either.
我也永远不会忘记你。
Oh yes.
哦是的。
Do you still remember?
你还记得吗？
During your wedding ceremony,
在您的婚礼期间，
Why did Zhao 'an call Ah Kun there?
赵安为什么把阿坤叫到那里？
Let go of my hand!
放开我的手！
I do not suspect the Left Cavalry,
我不怀疑左翼骑兵，
if not, can I allow him to come to work here?
如果不行的话我可以允许他来这里工作吗？
Why are you asking this question?
你为什么问这个问题？
Mari.
马里。
Sit down,
坐下，
Your behavior is really bad.
你的行为实在是太糟糕了。
Zhao 'an has fallen into the well.
赵安掉进井里了。
Still not breathing.
仍然没有呼吸。
We want to throw stones inside.
我们想往里面扔石头。
What stone?
什么石头？
You should be able to find Zhao 'an's evidence
你应该能找到赵安的证据
you need to find evidence that Zhao 'an is still guilty.
你需要找到赵安仍然有罪的证据。
When you say that,
当你这么说的时候，
(I remembered something else strange.)
（我想起了一些奇怪的事情。）
On my wedding day,
在我结婚那天，
feng Qi went first?
风起先走了？
Before the wedding,
婚礼前，
Zhao 'an told Feng Seven something.
赵安告诉了凤七一件事。
Feng seven left in a hurry.
凤七匆匆离开。
Probably nothing to do with
可能与以下无关
with the hero's murder at the foot of the mountain,
随着英雄在山下的被杀，
but always make others remember.
但总要让别人记住。
Then, go scheme Feng Qi.
然后，去算计冯琪。
No, how do I investigate?
不行，我该如何调查？
I investigated without evidence.
我调查过，没有证据。
What if something happens to him?
万一他出了事怎么办？
Actually,
实际上，
remind you
提醒你
Doesn't it make you suspicious?
这难道不会让你产生怀疑吗？
If there is any doubt, can you not investigate?
如果有疑问就不能不调查吗？
Of course no problem.
当然没问题。
Isn't it better to investigate?
调查一下不是更好吗？
You don't know this theory.
你不知道这个理论。
That's right.
这是正确的。
Team leader.
队长。
I met the two Japanese people
我遇见了两个日本人
I met the two Japanese people.
我遇到了两个日本人。
But when followed to Mingzhe University,
但当跟随到明哲大学时，
after that disappear.
之后就消失了。
I've been looking here for a day.
我在这里找了一天了
Personal hair is not visible.
个人毛发是看不见的。
Wait for me there.
在那里等我。
I will come soon.
我很快就到。
Good.
好的。
Why so many people
为什么这么多人
why are so many people here today?
今天怎么这么多人在这里？
Dysentery has been going on for the past two days.
这两天一直有腹泻。
Many Japanese soldiers and their family members contracted the disease.
许多日本士兵及其家属都感染了这种疾病。
The hospital was full of people.
医院里挤满了人。
I'm sure,
我敢肯定，
they are both in the Army General Hospital.
他们都在陆军总医院。
I will act tomorrow morning.
我明天早上就行动。
You go to Army General Hospital to kill people?
你去陆军总医院杀人？
You don't want to die?
你不想死吗？
You have forgotten, Mr. Mumura once said,
你忘了，木村先生曾经说过，
this matter must be kept confidential.
这件事必须保密。
And don't involve us.
并且不要让我们参与其中。
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
Find the killer
找出凶手
entered the hospital disguised as a cleaner.
乔装成清洁工进入医院。
After the incident,
事件发生后，
remove badness let it end.
消除坏事让它结束。
Team leader.
队长。
You have thought carefully.
你已经仔细考虑过了。
I do now.
我现在做的。
I know the man in the gray robe.
我认识那个灰袍人。
He is a killer.
他是一个杀手。
He was nicknamed Handalan.
他的绰号是汉达兰。
There are several lives in my hands.
我手里有好几条人命。
Hiding in a French concession for several years.
躲藏在法租界数年。
But, the strange thing is,
但是，奇怪的是，
zhao 'an wants to kill people.
赵安想要杀人。
Why are his men not moving?
他的人为何不动？
Instead, find another killer.
相反，寻找另一个杀手。
After following this ghost,
跟随这个鬼魂之后，
we'll know who Zhao'an's target is.
我们就知道兆安的目标是谁了。
Do you want me to go with you?
你想让我和你一起去吗？
Let it be.
随它去。
He has long worked in the French concession.
他长期在法租界工作。
Maybe I've met you.
也许我见过你。
I went alone.
我一个人去的。
Be careful.
当心。
Is it time to negotiate?
是时候谈判了吗？
Of.
的。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I have told them to prepare.
我已经告诉他们要做好准备。
However, I hope our negotiations this time
不过，我希望我们这次的谈判
can run smoothly and successfully
可以顺利成功地运行
smoothly and successfully
顺利并成功
and captured China peacefully.
并和平占领了中国。
Of.
的。
Do not worry.
不用担心。
Both of you
你们俩
go to wards 1-3 on the ground floor.
前往一楼 1-3 号病房。
Why?
为什么？
Ward on the second floor...
病房在二楼...
Has been used as an isolation ward.
已被用作隔离病房。
Pack things.
收拾东西。
There is medicine spilled in this medicine room.
这间药房里有药物洒落。
Please go clean up.
请去清理一下。
Okay.
好的。
Good!
好的！
I'm a killer!
我是杀手！
Someone is spending money to kill you.
有人花钱要杀你。
There are also people who spend money to get information
也有人花钱获取信息
which one is your policy?
您的政策是哪一项？
I guess,
我猜，
but I need more people to get information.
但我需要更多人来获取信息。
So, if you tell me...
所以，如果你告诉我...
The information I want,
我想要的信息，
I will let you both go.
我会让你们俩走的。
My patience has its limits.
我的耐心是有限度的。
How do we deal with it?
我们该如何处理呢？
Can't say
不能说
he will kill us.
他会杀了我们。
Tell him false information.
告诉他虚假信息。
How did he find us?
他是怎么找到我们的？
Is to communicate closely
就是要密切沟通
secret leak of peace talks?
和谈秘密泄露？
Apparently, I can only profit less.
显然，我只能赚得更少。
Don't.
不。
Who?
WHO？
Why did Zhao 'an send an assassin
赵安为何派刺客
kill the two Japanese?
杀掉两个日本人？
Who are these two Japanese people?
这两个日本人是谁？
Are they pro-China or anti-war?
他们是亲华还是反战？
Unfortunately, I don't understand Japanese
可惜我不懂日语
some Japanese words.
一些日语单词。
Left, two pics.
左图两张。
Act smart.
行事聪明。
Defying military orders,
违抗军令，
not only remove secret letters that are difficult to find...
不仅删除难以找到的秘密信件......
Hard to get,
很难得到，
in fact, dare to continue hiding.
其实还敢继续躲。
Is it your superiors?
是你的上级吗？
or no organization?
或者没有组织？
I think definitely taken by
我认为肯定被
taken by people in the store.
被店里的人拍的。
So, I kept lurking,
于是我就一直潜伏着
I will definitely be able to find it again.
我一定能再次找到它。
You feel everything
你感受到一切
It's easy to hide, isn't it?
隐藏起来很容易，不是吗？
Luo Guanqun.
Luo Guanqun.
Tell me to work in a commercial bank in three days.
叫我三天后去商业银行上班。
Add to that my brother's father's relationship with Yu Shanren,
再加上我哥的父亲和于山人的关系，
I can definitely succeed.
我一定能成功。
Don't think I don't know.
别以为我不知道。
If you continue to live in Shanghai,
如果你继续住在上海，
don't you want to stay with Chen Jiaping?
你不想留在陈家平身边吗？
I do not have.
我没有。
Don't quibble.
别狡辩。
I disobeyed orders.
我违抗命令。
Please give me punishment.
请给我惩罚。
Do not miss to punish you,
不要错过惩罚你，
I can execute the death penalty for you.
我可以替你执行死刑。
I won't regret it.
我不会后悔的。
You are stubborn.
你很固执。
I let you stay in Shanghai.
我让你留在上海。
What is your mission?
你的使命是什么？
he worked at a merchant bank
他在一家商业银行工作
to keep looking for information.
继续寻找信息。
Of.
的。
The truth will emerge after acting.
行动之后，真相就会浮出水面。
Watch movie?
看电影？
Candlelight dinner.
烛光晚餐。
All your behavior
你所有的行为
like a newly married couple.
就像一对新婚夫妇。
But the most important thing is
但最重要的是
don't let Chen Jiaping doubt you.
别让陈家平怀疑你。
Of.
的。
I will get the job done!
我会完成工作的！
We can no longer disobey orders.
我们不能再违抗命令了。
It's your turn now.
轮到你了。
Find me for what?
找我干什么？
Before Miss Hanlu
韩露小姐之前
have collaborated with
曾与
with Manchuria, right?
与满洲，对吗？
Of.
的。
If so, it seems,
如果是这样的话，看来，
you too
你也是
Miss Hanlu is very good at Japanese, right?
韩露小姐日语很厉害吧？
I don't dare to say that I am completely proficient.
我不敢说我​​完全精通。
There is no problem in normal communication.
正常通讯没有问题。
Actually this is how it is.
其实是这样的。
I want to ask Miss Han Lu to help me
我想请韩露小姐帮帮我
translate some Japanese words to me.
翻译一些日语单词给我听。
However, it is not a complete sentence.
然而，这并不是一个完整的句子。
Just a few paragraphs.
就几段。
After all, my pronunciation might not be good enough.
毕竟我的发音可能还不够好。
Speak up.
说出来。
I tried.
我试过。
Thank You.
谢谢。
I copied it on paper.
我把它抄在纸上。
And mention the peace talks with the Chongqing government.
并提到与重庆政府的和谈。
Another secret leak.
又一个秘密泄露。
Chongqing government peace talks.
重庆政府和谈。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Besides that,
除此之外，
don't tell anyone.
不要告诉任何人。
Yes?
是的？
That's right.
这是正确的。
Talk to smart people
与聪明人交谈
This is so exciting.
这太令人兴奋了。
Miss Han Lu,
韩璐女士，
you have to keep a secret for me again.
你又要为我保守秘密了。
I already know
我已经知道了
men have many secrets.
男人有很多秘密。
Keep a secret
保守秘密
It has to keep a lot of secrets.
它必须保守很多秘密。
Miss Lu must be
卢小姐一定是
also a person who has many secrets, right?
也是一个有很多秘密的人吧？
Maybe someday,
也许有一天，
I will tell you my secret.
我会告诉你我的秘密。
Team leader, team leader.
团队领导者，团队领导者。
Have you run?
你跑了吗？
where have you gone
你去哪儿了
I've been looking for a long time near the hospital, but I can't find it.
我在医院附近找了好久，也没找到。
Feng Qi.
Feng Qi.
Why do you use two knives?
为什么要用两把刀？
There is no perfect solution.
没有完美的解决方案。
Worse.
更差。
Not.
不是。
If not suddenly there is a fake doctor,
如果不是突然出现了一个假医生，
this operation will succeed.
此操作将会成功。
Fake doctor!
假医生！
Did you see that?
你看到了吗？
He wore a face covering.
他戴着面罩。
But you can't see his face clearly.
但你看不清他的脸。
Why did you take me to see the movie?
你为什么带我去看电影？
After marriage, can't watch movies?
结婚后就不能看电影了？
Yes.
是的。
But why did you invite me to see Hanlu's movie?
但你为什么邀请我看韩璐的电影呢？
Didn't think he was already acting.
没想到他已经开始演戏了。
I want to know, I will definitely not buy!
我想知道，我是绝对不会买的！
Go away!
离开！
Are you really mad?
你真的生气了吗？
I went to the toilet.
我去了趟厕所。
Pic two from left.
图左二。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I should ask you.
我应该问你。
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Why pretend to be a peddler?
为什么要冒充小贩？
Why don't you leave Shanghai?
你为什么不离开上海？
I...
我...
Must act properly.
必须采取正确的行动。
Watch movie?
看电影？
Candlelight dinner.
烛光晚餐。
All your behavior
你所有的行为
like a newly married couple.
就像一对新婚夫妇。
Why do you want to kill Chen Jiaping?
为什么要杀陈家平？
This is an order.
这是命令。
He still has a function.
他还有一个功能。
He can't die.
他不能死。
I can't submit my assignment.
我无法提交我的作业。
Apparently, let me watch a movie with Chen Jiaping
看来是让我和陈家平一起看电影
This is a conspiracy.
这是一个阴谋。
He should choose legal concessions.
他应该选择法律让步。
Why?
为什么？
Easy to escape after success.
成功后很容易逃脱。
Captain Liu told me to do this.
刘队长让我这么做的。
I think there must be a reason.
我想这一定是有原因的。
Go back.
回去。
I will explain to Captain Liu.
我去给刘队长解释一下。
I promise I won't bother him, okay?
我保证不会打扰他，好吗？
Look,
看，
before this
在这之前
managed to kill the mountain foot warrior.
成功击杀了山脚战士。
You trust me,
你信任我，
right?
正确的？
Of.
的。
Lu's most exciting plan had just passed.
陆最激动的计划刚刚过去。
Look at it.
看它。
I eat kuaci.
我吃夸茨。
Look at your cold dew.
看看你的冷露。
Very well acted.
演得很好。
Since you're shopping, I'm watching a movie,
既然你在购物，我在看电影，
what do you say I buy you dinner?
你说我请你吃饭怎么样？
do you want to eat
你想吃东西吗
Follow your words.
按照你的话去做。
Follow me.
跟我来。
Jiaping.
Jiaping.
How much Hanlu.
寒露多少。
Can you sign for me?
你可以帮我签名吗？
Good.
好的。
That's right.
这是正确的。
Celebrities are different.
名人则不同。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Hello, Jiaping.
你好，嘉平。
Do not rush.
不着急。
Don't be impulsive.
不要冲动。
Friend.
朋友。
Do not act recklessly.
切勿鲁莽行事。
What do you want to know?
你想知道什么？
what do you want,
你想要什么，
can just say
只能说
Do not act recklessly.
切勿鲁莽行事。
Put the gun down.
把枪放下。
Don't come here.
别来这里。
Otherwise, I'll shoot you!
不然我就开枪打死你！
According to the words of the two pics,
根据两张照片的文字，
Chen Jiaping was also there at that time.
当时陈家平也在场。
A difficult letter was in his hands.
他手里拿着一封难读的信。
Since it cannot be taken back,
既然无法收回，
no possibility to leak.
没有泄漏的可能性。
You must remember.
你一定要记住。
If Chen Jiaping lives one more day,
如果陈家平多活一天，
Another day of more danger for Double Peach left.
对于双桃来说，又是更加危险的一天。
For the sake of the left twin pic,
为了左边的双胞胎照片，
I will definitely complete this task!
我一定会完成这个任务的！
Do not see.
别看。
Don't look again.
别再看了。
Take him away.
把他带走。
you nothing?
你什么都没有？
I was surprised.
我很惊讶。
Jiaping.
Jiaping.
are you good
你好吗
How Lu.
何卢.
You're welcome.
不客气。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Remind me
提醒我
Who is he?
他是谁？
Why do you want to kill me?
你为什么要杀我？
I don't know either.
我也不知道。
Anti-japanese, right?
抗日吧？
Cheng Zi.
Cheng Zi.
You manage the shooting this time.
这次你负责拍摄。
Cannot be recorded in the file.
无法记录在文件中。
And cannot be known by journalists.
并且不能被记者知晓。
Besides that,
除此之外，
the body needs to be buried in a mass.
尸体需要被埋葬在一起。
All right. Do not worry.
好的。不用担心。
How much Hanlu.
寒露多少。
why are you here
你为什么在这
Every time my film is shown,
每次我的电影放映时，
will sit in the middle of the audience
将坐在观众中间
watch with them.
和他们一起观看。
Because, I want to know their reaction.
因为，我想知道他们的反应。
Oh yes.
哦是的。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
Mari.
马里。
I forgot to introduce you.
我忘了介绍你了。
This is my wife, Zuo Shuangtao.
这是我的妻子左双涛。
Helo.
你好。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
Okay.
好的。
Do you know him too?
你也认识他吗？
Must know.
必须知道。
China-Japan Goodwill Ambassador.
中日亲善大使。
Famous artist Han Lu.
著名艺术家韩露。
Actually, my profile is in many newspapers
事实上，我的个人资料出现在很多报纸上
not exactly.
不完全是。
I think it's quite right.
我认为这是非常正确的。
Jiaping.
Jiaping.
Didn't you say he was a fan?
你不是说他是粉丝吗？
I didn't think he was still a close friend.
我不认为他仍然是一个亲密的朋友。
I have only ever met Miss Han Lu.
我只见过韩露小姐。
You chat. I go first.
你们聊天。我先走了。
I will go with you.
我会和你一起去。
Don't come with me.
别跟我来。
I have my own business.
我有我自己的事情。
Jiaping.
Jiaping.
Did I misunderstand him?
我是不是误会他了？
No.
不。
You go back first.
你先回去吧。
I will explain to Captain Liu.
我去给刘队长解释一下。
I promise I won't trouble him.
我保证不会麻烦他。
Good?
好的？
Ah Kun.
阿坤。
Forgive me.
对不起。
Why don't you eat peaches for breakfast?
早餐为什么不吃桃子？
We had a falling out recently.
我们最近闹翻了。
We eat separately.
我们分开吃。
Their relationship became strained after only a few days of marriage.
结婚仅仅几天后，他们的关系就变得紧张。
Lao Lu.
Lao Lu.
Nothing. Sulking, arguing.
没有什么。生闷气，争吵。
Isn't this more like a couple?
这不是更像情侣吗？
That's right too.
这也是对的。
Lately, the Shan Plan has shown no progress.
最近，掸邦计划毫无进展。
But got an unexpected profit.
却得到了意想不到的收获。
What?
什么？
Did you hear that
你听到了吗
the Chongqing government and the Japanese government
重庆市政府和日本政府
with the Japanese government.
与日本政府。
Peace talks?
和平会谈？
A year ago,
一年前，
chiang kai-shek once signaled...
蒋介石曾发出信号...
Du Shishan, the person in charge of the Hong Kong office
香港办事处负责人 杜诗善
peace negotiations with Japan
与日本的和平谈判
also negotiated a pro-Japanese anti-communist policy.
还商定了亲日反共政策。
However, Japan decided to support Wang Jingwei.
然而，日本却决定支持汪精卫。
The peace talks are finally over.
和谈终于结束了。
Peace talks will resume now.
和谈现在将恢复。
It seems there is still a trick on my side.
看来我这边还是有窍门的。
I have understood.
我明白了。
I will investigate the truth as soon as possible.
我会尽快调查真相。
There is one more thing.
还有一件事。
I think peaches are left growing
我认为桃子还在生长
has become increasingly suspicious recently.
最近变得越来越可疑。
Before Ah Kun died,
阿坤去世前，
before he died.
在他去世之前。
I suspect they know each other.
我怀疑他们互相认识。
Then, I remembered various doubts in the wedding ceremony.
然后，我就想起了婚礼上的各种疑惑。
They sure are a bunch
他们肯定是一群
or they were members of anti-Japanese organizations.
或者他们是抗日组织的成员。
But why does Ah Kun want to kill you?
但阿坤为什么要杀你？
Take the pic from the left.
从左边拍照片。
And insisted on working in a trading bank.
并坚持在贸易银行工作。
Maybe he also wants to sneak into the store?
或许他也想偷偷溜进店里？
However, my existence
然而我的存在
is the biggest threat to him.
是对他最大的威胁。
Left Cavalry, Peach wants to kill you.
左骑兵，桃子想杀了你。